Do you, do you
Think of me when it rains
A feeling, feeling
That you just can’t explain
Just can’t, no
Soft and cold
And yet so gentle
Let it envelop you again
You make my heart go
Pitter patter pitter patter pitter
The droplets falling like I fell for you
But I, but I
Can’t shake the cloudy weather blues
I’m trying not to get soaked
In this dream that you are dreaming too
Why does your love just feel so bad for me
My mind is filling up with you, and it’s so baffling
And every time I speak
the words are stuck in my cheeks
Wanna be near you, but my heart is weak
I'm drowning in your love, baby
I can’t explain it
Washing me right out to sea
I have to face it
I’m going under
going under
And losing my breath
But please just let me swim
So I can see what’s next
potsuripotsuri ame ga furidashite
ajisai ga kanaderu warutsu
anata e no kimochi o tsubuyaku kedo
amaoto ni kakikesarete shimau
aiai kasa o shitai keredo
fumidasu yuuki wa mada nai yo
dou ka kono ame ga yamu mae ni
watashi no kimochi tsutaetaiyo
anata no koi ni oboreteru yo
setsumei dekinai kedo
umi ni nagasareru you ni
mukaiawanai to
ikigurushiku te mo
te o tada oyogasete kudasai
tsugini nani ga okoru ka
wakaru you ni
drowning in your love, baby
I can’t explain it
Washing me right out to sea
I have to face it
I’m going under
going under
And losing my breath
But please just let me swim...